Hello friends, the
results of ICICI Lord General Insurance Company have come,
now we will see how the company
presented its results for this quarter. If we look at the net
premium income, which is Rs
4467 crore in the last quarter, it has increased to Rs
crore this quarter. This time the income has increased
from the last quarter,
from the previous year and quarter on quarter is also
up, so the company has shown a very good income.
Now if we go down and see
what is the net profit of this quarter,
then the dividend has been given this quarter, the
final dividend is shown here,
Rs 580 crore per share here and if
we look at the net profit, how much is the
net profit, friends, and
last year it was only Rs 390 crore, there has been a
jump last year and
from the previous quarter it was only Rs 520 crore, so there has been a good
jump of Rs 10, quarter on quarter and
year on
year, there has been a jump of more than Rs 30, so we are getting
excellent results. We will
also see from ICICI Lombard and other segments from where this
company is making money. If we  If we
look at the earnings, the company is showing segment operating profit loss
here. So if we
see here, most of the money that is coming from their profit is
coming from motor, that is, vehicle
insurance, which they do, mostly like four
wheeler, this company does very well,
four wheeler and two wheeler and all the other
second highest income is coming
from fire, that is, corporate which have become golden
and commercial corporate companies which have become
buildings for fire, they insure them,
second highest income is coming from here,
these people are earning some money in marine, they are incurring
loss and in health insurance also they are
not making that much money today. Here,
their third highest profit is coming from miscellaneous corporate corporate insurance, so if we
look at their two large segments, then almost maximum income is coming from motor vehicle insurance
and fire,
so it is a very good
company, valuations are fine, right now it is
trading at 44 p, it is at 92000 crore market cap, it is a
little big right now, last
year the
company has given good returns, very good
Nice RO RE watch it overall
thumbs up for the ICC Labad results please
subscribe and like friends and share it to
help in making more videos